Come on,
what happened?   Will
you tell me why you are roaming around naked
?   I am not naked,
I am wearing a tower.
And where is the top one?   That's why
I forgot to take it with me.
No problem, just wear it now.  Wear it quickly.   I am not
wearing it.  I am wearing it.
[Music] I
wore it, I wore it.
Look, this won't work.  We have to set some ground
rules.
Yes, please tell me.
First rule, no roaming around naked.
Hey, I wasn't naked.  I was wearing a
towel?
Which is okay for you, but not for me.
Okay, no roaming around
naked. Second, your male friends are not allowed.
Okay, male friends are not allowed.
Third, no smoking, no drinking.
I don't drink or smoke.
Okay, and the fourth rule is your girlfriend is also
not allowed. If you want to meet her,
you have to meet her outside. No, don't worry, I don't have a
girlfriend.
Really, really,
I am so sorry. I didn't mean that. That's okay.
Now, I have become used to getting such
reactions. There are no other rules. This is all that came to my
mind. If anything
else comes to my mind, I will tell you. By the way,
you had come to ask me something, right?
Now, before that towel incident, you had come to
ask me something,
oh yes, name, address, occupation. Do you
want a list of name, address, occupation? Your
landlord has asked for that.
Ok.  I will bring it right away.  I have arranged everything.
One second.
Take this.   Thank
you.
I think you might want to say something down there.   Yes sir
?
Ok sir.  Ok.
You can't new.  It's okay.
Yes, yes,
all the insults will happen today itself.
[music]